A Guide to the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia, Committee Records, 1953-2000
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1995 (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee 1995 Jun-1997 Jun (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence (2 folders) 1996-1998 (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 58)
- Study of Organization of University, Special Committee on--Minutes 1966-1967 (Box 58)
- Teaching Awards 1979-1980 (Box 58)
- Thomas Jefferson Award Committee 1979-1987 (Box 58)
- Thomas Jefferson 250th Birthday Committee 1992 (Box 58)
- RESTRICTED (Box 59)